Contact

toufikaminew@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/taoufika (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Virtual Private Network (VPN)
Voice over IP (VoIP)
Wireless Technologies

Languages

French (Native or Bilingual)

Python (Limited Working)

HTML (Professional Working)

Certifications

CompTIA Security+ (SY0-601)
Cert Prep: 1 Threats, Attacks, and
Vulnerabilities

Windows 10: Administration

Securing Windows Server 2016: Server Hardening Solutions

Securing Windows Server 2019

Windows Server 2019: Manage, Monitor, and Maintain Servers

Taoufik A

Aspiring CyberSecurity professional with Computer Science BA degree and 10+ years experience working in IT as a senior computer engineer/system admin.

United States

Summary

Aspiring CyberSecurity professional with a Computer Science BA degree, and 10+ years experience working in IT as a senior computer engineer, system admin by day, and web designer by night which helped me accumulate couple of years experience working as a freelancer web designer working on couple clients' web projects and building my own websites as a hobby.

Currently transferring my extensive IT and coding skills, experience and knowledge towards specializing in Cybersecurity thru pursuing Security+ Cert and completing the Cybersecurity Bootcamp at Springboard."

Experience

HCL Technologies
Desktop Support Specialist
February 2020 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Freelancer.com
Web Designer
January 2021 - May 2021 (5 months)

Tenet Healthcare

Taleo HealthStream Tier II Remote Support Specialist August 2019 - January 2020 (6 months)

NEC Corporation
Level 2 Support Technician
October 2018 - December 2019 (1 year 3 months)

Pei Wei

Tier III Restaurant Support Analyst January 2018 - April 2019 (1 year 4 months) Brinker International
Client Support Professional
January 2017 - January 2018 (1 year 1 month)

D&H Distributing
Cloud Client Support Professional
January 2016 - May 2017 (1 year 5 months)

EarthLink Internet
Desktop Support Engineer
January 2012 - January 2016 (4 years 1 month)

Education

Springboard

· (May 2021 - November 2021)

University at Buffalo

Master of Technology - MTech, Computer Science · (2016 - 2018)

Franklin University

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Information Technology Project Management · (2009 - 2013)

The Ohio State University

Associate's degree, Information Technology (2007 - 2009)